Bojan Elez

Software Engineer



- belez911@gmail.com
- +381 60 67 98 204
- Atinska 103A/8, Kragujevac, Serbia
- Serbian
- **31.01.1991**

Education

- Prva Tehnicka Skola2006 2010
- Faculty of Engineering2010 2015

Languages

English

Skills

HTML & CSS

Javascript

TypeScript

Tailwind

React

NextIS

Redux

NodeJS

Express

SQL

lest

React Query

Storybook

Material Ui

Git

GraphQL

Summary

Hi, I'm a Software Engineer with 6 years of experience in HTML, CSS, React, Node.js and little bit of Backend experience. I enjoy using creativity and technology to make user-friendly web-apps. I'm good at solving tough problems and creating scalable apps. I'm always eager to learn and keep up with industry trends. I work well in teams and believe in clear communication.

I love building websites and web- apps, from my point of view I am trying write clean and maintainable code and web-apps with good UX.

I am looking for a company willing to offer me a placement among their developers. In return, I would offer my full commitment, and be a pleasant and friendly addition to your team. I am currently looking for a new job as a front-end developer. Every day I learn new things and try to improve myself as a Developer.

I'm excited to contribute my skills and passion to your development team.

Work Experience

Software Engineer, Orion Innovation, Belgrade

December 2023 - Present

Role: Fronted Developer, Domain: Wealth Management

Developed and maintained client-facing financial dashboards for a leading wealth management platform, enhancing user experience for advisors and investors.

Built & maintain Micro Frontends (MFE) to modularize complex UI components, improving scalability and team autonomy. Conducted functional testing (Jest, React Testing Library) to ensure reliability and compliance with financial data standards.

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, Styled Components, React Query, Material UI, React, Zustand, MFE, Jest Testing Library

Role: Frontend Developer, Domain: Telecommunication

I contributed to a telecomunication project. My role involved developing engaging and interactive user interfaces, with a specific focus on enhancing the user experience and visual appeal of the platform. I worked to create an engaging platform contact center.

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, Material UI, React Query, React, Jest Testing Library

Software Engineer, Novi Sad, Vega IT

November 2022 - November 2023

Role: Full-Stack Developer, Domain: Construction Industry

This project was also built from scratch, utilizing cutting-edge technologies. The main objective was to enable the app to work offline, optimizing workflow efficiency in the construction industry. Specifically, the project involved creating an inspection app for houses, designed for inspectors to enter values ranging from dimensions of doors and windows to types of solar panels, all while ensuring seamless offline functionality.

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, Material UI, Redux Toolkit, React, PWA, NodeJS

Role: Backend Developer, Domain: Blockchain

On this project, I primarily worked on the back-end, using NodeJS, SQL, and OpenSearch. The project focused on implementing blockchain technology to enhance data security and transparency, specifically in monitoring the process from the origin of the material to the end customer. My role included designing and implementing robust backend systems to support this extensive monitoring process.

Tech Stack: NodeJS, Express, SQL

Frontend Developer, Novi Sad, EXLRT

December 2020 - October 2022

Role: Frontend Developer, Domain: Travel & Education

Working on the STS Education project, I was responsible for frontend development tasks in React. I maintained user interfaces, ensuring a user-friendly experience for students and travelers. I work with API's and EPI Server CMS.

Tech Stack: HTML, SCSS, React, EPiServer

Role: Frontend Developer, Domain: Healthcare

As a Frontend Developer on the Healthcare project, I contributed to the development of a healthcare solution. My role included implementing user interfaces and collaborating with the back-end team to ensure seamless data integration and functionality. This project is designed with accessibility in mind, ensuring an inclusive experience for all users.

Frontend Developer, Kragujevac, Innovation Cloud

December 2018 - December 2020

Role: Full Stak Developer, Domain: Innovation

I was involved in redesigning a couple of apps related to Innovation Management platform. First Couple of months I was intern later I got mine first programing job.

Tech Stack: HTML, LESS, JQuery, Responsive Design, PHP, MySQL